So in our previous section we have seen how to update Mifare classic card using ACR 1 to 2 tool.
In this section we are going to update the same Mifare classic card, but using this MFC 5 to 2 STM
eight microcontroller.
So this is the board we are going to use.
So it has the same chip which we have used before in our earlier sections.
The MFC 5 to 2 Chip.
But this board also contains this STM chip over here.
This STM microcontroller.
So first we will program this STM eight microcontroller and using this microcontroller, we will operate
this MFC 5 to 2 Chip and we will read, write and update data using this STM eight microcontroller.
So to operate on this board, we need two other things as well.
The first thing we need is USB to TTL cable, which is over here in Silver Color, you can see.
And the other thing is STM eight and Stm32 USB, which you can easily purchase from Amazon or AliExpress.
So all these things you can easily purchase from Amazon or AliExpress.
These are the tools which we are going to use.
Now let me just go through the cost of these tools real quick.
So the cost of hardware MFC 5 to 2 with STM microcontroller.
This is the board which we are going to use and it will cost you around 4 to $5.
Then USB two cable, we will use USB two cable to operate on Mifare classic card and we will use STM
eight and Stm32 USB, which is the same USB for STM eight and stm32.
This is the USB over here and we will use this USB to program our STM eight microcontroller.
Right.
So this is the cost of USB two cable, then STM eight and STM 32 USB will cost you around 3 to $5.
So the complete cost of all these hardware is around $10, which is quite less than 1 to 2 module,
which was around 25 to $30.
So these are the hardware requirements and the both the softwares for this tool are free.
So you can easily download these two software.
The first one is STB, which is a software to program STM eight microcontroller.
And the other tool is MFC 5 to 2, which is a software we will use to, you know, update our Mifare
classic card through this software.
So make sure you download these two softwares as well.